Mercy O. Avwenagbiku

Front-End Web Developer

My journey into web development started over two years ago and in the course of that period, I have grown tremendously. I am passionate about continuous learning and self-development. A meticulous person that pays attention to details. Experience with working with a team, building websites from concept to launch.

Experience

Front-End Developer

Freelancer

Sept, 2020 - till date

- Design a user-friendly web application for clients using Figma.
- Build a responsive web application from concept to deployment.
- Maintenance of websites for clients to optimize the latest development.
- Build SEO optimized websites.

Tutor

Chemscrystals Ltd (Part-time)

Jan, 2020 - till date

- Tutor high school kids' web development using HTML and CSS.
- Tutor young kids coding using Scratch programming language.
- Developed curriculum to enable smooth and interactive classes.

Education

Masters of Technology

Food Science

Lanzhou University of Technology, Lanzhou, Gansu, China

2017-2020

Bachelor of Technology

Food Science and Technology

Federal University of Technology, Akure, Ondo, Nigeria

2007-2012

Personal Information

Address

#6, Maxwell Ijeh Crescent, Aguda, Surulere, Lagos, Nigeria.

Phone Number

+2347066489259

Email

messiovo@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mercyavwenagbiku-09414a80/

Github

https://github.com/messiovo

Skills

Hyper Text Markup Language

(HTML)

Excellent

Cascading Style Sheet (CSS)

Intermediate

JavaScript (JS)

Intermediate

React-JS

Intermediate

UX/ UI Design (Figma)

Intermediate

Languages

English



Proficient

Mandarin



Intermediate